♪ ♪
♪ THOUGHT I FOUND A WAY ♪
♪ THOUGHT I FOUND
A WAY OUT (OUT) ♪
♪ BUT YOU NEVER GO AWAY
(NEVER GO AWAY) ♪
♪ SO I GUESS
I GOTTA STAY NOW ♪
♪ OH I HOPE SOMEDAY
I'LL MAKE IT OUT OF HERE ♪
♪ EVEN IF IT TAKES ALL NIGHT
OR A HUNDRED YEARS ♪
♪ NEED A PLACE TO HIDE
BUT I CAN'T FIND ONE NEAR ♪
♪ WANNA FEEL ALIVE OUTSIDE
I CAN'T FIGHT MY FEAR ♪
♪ ISN'T IT LOVELY? ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ HEART MADE OF GLASS
MY MIND OF STONE ♪
♪ TEAR ME TO PIECES ♪
♪ SKIN TO BONE ♪
♪ HELLO ♪
♪ WELCOME HOME. ♪
♪ WALKING OUT OF TIME ♪
♪ LOOKING FOR
A BETTER PLACE ♪
♪ SOMETHING'S ON MY MIND ♪
♪ MIND ♪
♪ ALWAYS IN MY HEAD SPACE ♪
♪ BUT I KNOW SOMEDAY
I'LL MAKE IT OUT OF HERE ♪
♪ EVEN IF IT TAKES ALL NIGHT
OR A HUNDRED YEARS ♪
♪ NEED A PLACE TO HIDE
BUT I CAN'T FIND ONE NEAR ♪
♪ WANNA FEEL ALIVE OUTSIDE
I CAN'T FIGHT MY FEAR ♪
♪ ISN'T IT LOVELY? ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ HEART MADE OF GLASS
MY MIND OF STONE ♪
♪ TEAR ME TO PIECES ♪
♪ SKIN TO BONE ♪
♪ HELLO, ♪
♪ WELCOME HOME ♪
♪ [KALID: VOCALIZING] ♪
♪ [BILLIE: VOCALIZING] ♪
♪ ♪
♪ HELLO,
WELCOME HOME ♪